BARBARA SAGREDO

• Jr. Front end developer - Editorial photographer •

ABOUT ME

I'm a chilean woman currently living in NZ with a working holiday visa. I'll be here one year working and travelling the country, so I'm really excited to make this experience a great time.

What most motivates me is to practice my english and be able to learn all I can from this experience.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017 • Arcos Profesional Institute, Editorial Photographer.

2020 • Laboratoria Latam, Front end Developer.

EXPERIENCE

2022 Kawchi

Junior Front end Developer

- Attend the daily meeting where the tasks of the day are organized.
- Responsible for creating and maintaining Kawchi website software components following Figma's design.
- Propose technical and design improvements.

2018-2019 Red Salud Uc-Christus

Administrative secretary at a health clinic

• Attend to the requests of different areas of the health center, mainly schedule and change care schedules of the doctors.

2012 - 2017 Caramel Café Paine

Coffee shop employee.

- Customer service.
- Making and serving different types of coffee, sandwiches, pizzas.
- In addition to cashier, store closing as well as cleaning and order.

SKILLS

English level medium	\bigcirc	Aesthetic sense	
Organization	⊘	Commited to learn	Ø
Proactivity	\bigcirc	Constancy	②